Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
- Series IV. Professional Papers Writings Books
  - CS 100, 1980 (2) (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - CS 101, 1981-1982 (1) (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - CS 101, 1981-1982 (2) (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - CS 101, 1981-1982 (3) (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Engr 202 Student Notes(Marcus Wilson), 1991-1992 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1982 (1) (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1982 (2) (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1983 (1) (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - CS 280Fall, 1983 (2) (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1983 (3) (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1983 (4) (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - CS 280 Fall Course Materials (1), 1983 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - CS 280 Course Materials (2), 1983 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - CS 280 Course Materials (3), 1983 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1985 (1) (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1985 (2) (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1985 (3) (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1988 (1) (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1988 (2) (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1988 (3) (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - CS 280Fall, 1989 (1) (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1989 (2) (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1990 (1) (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - CS 280 Fall, 1990 (2) (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - CS 305 Fall, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - CS 280 Logarithms, Number Theory, Permutations, Recurrence (1), n.d. (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - (2), n.d. (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - (3), n.d. (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - CS 305 Final Exam and Student Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - CS 305 Final Exam (Fall), 1976 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - CS 305, 1976-1977 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - CS 305 Fall Handouts, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - CS 305 Fall, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - CS 305 Book 2, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 30-32)
  - CS 305 Readings, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - CS 305, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
  - CS 305 Privacy, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - CS 305, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 6-8)
  - CS 305, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - CS 305 Book 1, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 10-12)
  - CS 409 Sorting (Iverson), 1962-1971 (Box 80, Folder 13-14)
  - CS 409, 1969-1977 (Box 80, Folder 15-17)
  - CS 409 Administration/Problems, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 18-19)
  - CS 410 Fall, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - CS 410 Fall, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - CS 410 Fall Final, 1974-1975 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - CS 410 Summer, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 23-28)
  - CS 432 Spring, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
  - CS 432 Book II, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 3-4)
  - CS 435, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - CS 435, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 6-7)
  - CS 635 Fall, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - CS 632 Fall, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - CS 632, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 10-12)
  - CS 632, 1978-1985 (Box 81, Folder 13-14)
  - CS 632 Fall, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - CS 632, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 16-18)
  - CS 632, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 19-20)
  - CS 632 Fall, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 21-22)
  - CS 632 Fall, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - CS 632 Fall, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 24-26)
  - CS 632 Fall, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 29-31)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - CS 635 Projects, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Summer Short Course Correspondence and Notes, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - CS 635 References and Notes, 1977-1981 (Box 82, Folder 5-7)
  - CS 635 Donna Bergman, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 8-10)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 11-14)
  - CS 635, 1980-1981 (Box 82, Folder 15-16)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 17-18)
  - CS 635 Course Notes, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 19-21)
  - CS 635 Tech Reports, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 24-25)
  - CS 635 Reports on SMART System (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - CS 635 Spring 1986 I (Box 82, Folder 28-29)
  - CS 635 Spring 1986 II (Box 82, Folder 30-31)
  - CS 635 Spring 1986 II (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - CS 635 Term Projects, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 2-4)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 6-7)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1989-1990 (Box 83, Folder 10-11)
  - CS 635 Homework/Exams, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 12-13)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1989-1990 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 15-16)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 17-18)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - CS 635 Spring Assignment #4, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - CS 635 Spring Assignment #5, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 21-22)
  - CS 635 Student Projects, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - CS 635 Final Exams, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - CS 739 Spring, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 26-28)
  - CS 635 Spring Term Book I, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 29-30)
  - CS 739, 1977-1978 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - CS 739 Hypertext Talk, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - CS 739 (1), 1994 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - CS 739 (2), 1994 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Seminar 739, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Computers and Legal Information Retrieval, Bibliography and Photocopies (1), 1966-1969 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Computers and Legal Information Retrieval, Bibliography and Photocopies (2), 1966-1969 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Computers and the Law (1), Spring 1974 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Computers and the Law (2), Spring 1974 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Computers and the Law (3), Spring 1974 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Computer Science and the Law Vol. 1 (1), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Computer Science and the Law Vol. 1 (2), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 2 (1), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 2 (2), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 2 (3), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 3 (1), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 3 (2), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 3 (3), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 4 (1), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 4 (2), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 4 (3), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 5 (1), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - C.S. and the Law Vol. 5 (2), 1968 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Cards: Pattern Recognition E. gcc. Stereotype. Prof. Salton Computation Laboratory, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Cards: Info Processing Talk, Princeton Talk, Linguistics, also FGCC Phila., 1962 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Cards: Prof. Gerard Salton Room 22 Computation Lab, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Summer Courses, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Summer Courses (1), 1973-1976 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Summer Courses (2), 1973-1976 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Summer Short Course, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Summer Info. Ret. Short Course, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Summer Course, 1977/1978 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Extra Text Processing, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Handouts (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Xerox Copies (1), 1964 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Xerox Copies (2), 1964 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Student Term Reports, Fall 1967-Fall 1972 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - C.S. Students, Spring 1973 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Student Term Reports, Spring 1975 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - T.A. Assignments, Spring 1982 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Notes, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Student Awards, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Humboldt Award, 1987-1988 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Awards, 1975-1985 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - G.S. Awards, 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Fellowship Info, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Serials (1), 1994-1996 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Serials (2), 1990, 1971-1973 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Info Retrieval Survey, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Staff Misc., 1994 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Phone Numbers, Commands, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Address Lists-Directory, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - SMART Plans, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Staff Lists, 1954-1965 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Talks, Who's Who, News Clippings, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Figures/Drawings, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Slides, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Diagrams, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Old Vellums (Overhead Projector Slides), n.d. (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Vellums (Basic System Slides), n.d. (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Old Slides, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Biographical/Bibliographies, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Transcripts, 1952-1958 (Box 85, Folder 36)
  - G.S. Commencement Program, June 14, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 37)
  - Employment Status Letters, 1952-1991 (Box 85, Folder 38)
  - Gerard Salton Biography, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 39)
  - Vitae (1), n.d. (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - Vitae (2), n.d. (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - Vitae (3), n.d. (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - Cornell Sponsored Programs, Chronicle and Misc. (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Dept Info and Subscriptions (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Univac II Manual, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Salton Resumes Research, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Salton Literature, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Misc., n.d. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Ithaca Yacht Club and Freeman (Boat), 1977-1982 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Ellen Binswanger Louis Papers, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Personal Items, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Lecture Poster, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Awards, 1958-1985 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Stenotype Dictionary, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Linear Stenotype Test and Stenotype Phrase Dictionary, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Business Cards, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 1-3)
  - Membership Cards, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Info. Ref. and Addresses (Box 88, Folder 5-6)
  - IBM Port-A-Punch Board, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - IBM Port-A-Punch Cards and Instructions (Box 88, Folder 8-9)
  - 30 Years of Information Retrieval at Cornell. A SMART Celebration. Tapes 1, 2, and 3 (Master Copy), April 22, 1995 (Box 89)
    Contains talks by Chris Buckley, Robert Constable, Donna Harman, Michael McGill, David Evans, Michael Lesk, Edward Fox, Karen Sparck Jones, Keith van Rijsbergen, William Cooper, W. Bruce Croft, and Gerard Salton.
  - 30 Years of Information Retrieval at Cornell. A SMART Celebration. Tapes 1, 2, and 3 (Use Copy), April 22, 1995; Also DVD-523 (Box 89)
  - Full Text Information Retrieval, March 12, 1993 (Box 89)
  - Salton Slides, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Computing Money: Slides, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Slides, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 3)